<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<documents xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
<doc id="1">
<title>
7ft 2in policeman is local celebrity - even among the criminals
</title>
<body>
Standing 2.2m (7ft 2in) tall, the 25-year-old police officer has a reach of almost a metre and needs size 17 boots to walk his beat.
But, despite his lofty stature, colleagues know the father of one as the BFG because of his friendly nature.
PC Wallyn, from Coulsdon, London, is something of a celebrity with tourists who often queue up to take his picture.
Even criminals chased by the 146kg (23st) rugby player ask for a photograph before being brought to book.
‘To be honest, 99 per cent of the reaction I get is positive, especially from tourists,’ he said.
‘When I’m near the Houses of Parliament, everyone wants a picture of me near Big Ben.
‘In the West End, when people are having a good time and the alcohol is flowing, it can be a challenge but I don’t let it get in the way of the job.’
PC Warren, who has a 142cm (56in) chest and an inside leg measurement of 93cm (37in), joined the Metropolitan Police two-and-a-half years ago. All his work clothes are custom made.
He said: ‘There wasn’t a uniform big enough at first so I had to spend 15 weeks in civvy clothes which my colleagues thought was very amusing.’
</body>
<url>
http://www.metro.co.uk/weird/882097-7ft-2in-policeman-is-local-celebrity-even-among-the-criminals
</url>
</doc>

<doc id="2">
<title>
Mystery gerbil ballerina dances his way into nation's hearts
</title>
<body>
This furry critter loves nothing more than being 'en pointe' - especially when he gets rewarded with a spot of grub for his troubles.
Twirling away to Mozart's Violin Concerto No.3 in G Major, Gary (this is probably not his name, by the way) shows excellent style and posture to earn the plaudits of his owners, and his thousands of YouTube fans.
'He looks like he's enjoying himself,' one observer commented upon seeing the 30-second clip.
One of the main stylistic features of contemporary ballet is the outward rotation of the thighs from the hip - a technique demonstrated with enviable poise by Gary.
Most ballet dancers would probably balk at the idea of being rewarded with a snack for every complete rotation, especially as having complete control of your bodyweight is a major component of modern dance.
But not this one. Gary retains his love of grub while also showing his talent on the stage. The Bolshoi awaits.
</body>
<url>
http://www.metro.co.uk/weird/882028-mystery-gerbil-ballerina-dances-his-way-into-nations-hearts
</url>
</doc>

<doc id="3">
<title>
Seven-year-old Indian girl Kura Nitya cries 'tears' of stone
</title>
<body>
According to a local newspaper, Kura has been excreting stones from her right eye for the last two weeks but doctors are not sure what is causing the phenomenon.
On average the young girl weeps between 12 to 25 stones a day. Nitya says she doesn't feel any pain but her right eye swells before the stones drop out.
Her grandfather Gopal Reddy says he first noticed the strange happenings in October. 'Initially, we thought it was some divine power and prayed to God for this phenomenon to stop,' he told the Star online.
The girl's parents have seen several different specialists but none have had an answer.
Ophthalmologist Dr Kalyan Chakaravarthy said Nitya was healthy and he could find no reason as to why she was weeping stones.
The stones have been kept for medical tests.
</body>
<url>
http://www.metro.co.uk/weird/882022-seven-year-old-indian-girl-kura-nitya-cries-tears-of-stone
</url>
</doc>

<doc id="4">
<title>
'Electric' blue lobster finds new home at London Aquarium after being saved
</title>
<body>
The deep-blue-coloured crustacean, which was caught by fishermen off the east coast of Scotland, was found by Rex Goldsmith on sale at Billingsgate market in London.
'It's the most striking blue lobster I have seen in my 30 years in the business and was too nice to put in a pot and boil,' said Goldsmith.
Shocked by the intense colour of the lobster, Rex decided to buy it and take it home with him to inform researchers at the National History Museum.
'I had a word with the seller and we both agreed on how nice it looked. He sold it to me for £10, which is the normal price for a lobster that size.'
The researchers believe the lobster gained its blue exterior because of a possible rare genetic alteration. Coming from a similar species of lobster to the homarus americanus of the US, the creature should have been born with a much darker blue exoskeleton. 
This particular species of lobster is found in British waters as well as in Norway, the Mediterranean, Crete and Morocco.
Yet to be given a proper name, Mr Goldsmith's find will now be on display at the London Aquarium.
</body>
<url>
http://www.metro.co.uk/weird/881934-electric-blue-lobster-finds-new-home-at-london-aquarium-after-being-saved
</url>
</doc>

<doc id="5">
<title>
Violence in Cairo leaves three dead as Egyptian security forces move in
</title>
<body>
The violence flared after thousands of demonstrators clashed with police over delays to political reforms in the country.
Some 5,000 demonstrators chanted 'freedom, freedom', throwing rocks and petrol bombs as they gathered in the capital's Tahrir Square, which was the focal point of the demonstrations which led to the toppling of President Hosni Mubarak in February.
Police fired tear gas and rubber bullets as the violence continued for a second day, following the fatal shooting of a 23-year-old protester on Saturday.
According to officials, around 900 people have been injured in the clashes.
The first post-Mubarak elections are due to start a week today. However the military has said it wants to hand over power after a new president is chosen late next year or in early 2013.
'The violence yesterday showed us that Mubarak is still in power,' said one demonstrator, Ahmed Hani.
</body>
<url>
http://www.metro.co.uk/news/882300-violence-in-cairo-leaves-three-dead-as-egyptian-security-forces-move-in
</url>
</doc>

<doc id="6">
<title>
40 per cent believe Britain would be better off out of European Union
</title>
<body>
Four in ten contend there would be a positive effect on the economy if Britain quit the union.
And nine out of ten are concerned about the effect the euro crisis is having on the British economy.
The eurozone has plunged into trouble following debt chaos in countries such as Greece, Italy and Ireland. There are also fears that the zone might break up.
Seven out of ten Britons told the survey they had followed the crisis in the news, with levels rising in line with the ages of those asked.
And the same number believe the British economy would have been affected more severely if the nation had adopted the euro.
Ukip leader Nigel Farage said: ‘The only people who will be surprised by these figures are the leadership of the three main parties.
‘Anybody who has bothered to talk to people across the country knows that leaving the European Union is the centre ground of British public opinion.’
He added: ‘The extremists are those who wish to keep us in it without the support of the people.’
However, Liberal Democrat MEP Chris Davies said Britain would continue to be bound by EU rules that the country had no influence over making.
‘Leaving the EU would result in decisions being made by the countries of central Europe by which we would inevitably be bound if we were to preserve our trading links,’ he said.
‘Those who are calling for Britain to pull out of the EU speak through ignorance of the facts or seek to betray Britain’s real interests.’
The Harris poll was conducted  online among 1,031 people aged over 16 in Britain, between November 8 and 15.
</body>
<url>
http://www.metro.co.uk/news/882336-40-per-cent-believe-britain-would-be-better-off-out-of-european-union
</url>
</doc>

<doc id="7">
<title>
Cristiano Ronaldo opens the door to shock Manchester United return
</title>
<body>
The Portuguese forward left Old Trafford for the Bernabeu in an £80million world-record deal in 2009, but confesses he still misses the hustle and bustle of the Premier League and won’t close the door on a shock comeback.
When asked about a potential return to England, he told Sky Sports News: ‘Maybe in the future I hope so, because I know the league, I know the players, I know the atmosphere.
‘I have good memories from Manchester and when I watch sometimes the games I miss it a lot because it's part of me I left in England.
‘The most important reason why I moved is the challenge because I really like to put myself under pressure to see what I can do, but I really miss the Premier League - for me it is along with the Spanish league the best league in the world.’
Ronaldo also praised the impact Sir Alex Ferguson had on his career, and reveals he still keeps in regular contact with the man that launched him on to the world stage.
‘Just because I play in Madrid I'm not going to miss speaking with the old guys so, when I have an opportunity, I speak with Sir Alex Ferguson,’ he added.
‘It was important for me when I played there, when my life was there, so it is good to speak with him because I'll never forget who really helped me.’
However, United fans shouldn't get too excited just yet, as the 26-year-old is loving life in the Spanish capital, and can't envisage a move in the near future.
'I am very, very happy in Madrid,' said Ronaldo.
'I've said a few times that, if Madrid want, I can sign for ten years more until the finish of my career but nobody knows the future.'
</body>
<url>
http://www.metro.co.uk/sport/football/874634-cristiano-ronaldo-opens-the-door-to-shock-manchester-united-return
</url>
</doc>

<doc id="8">
<title>
Silvio Berlusconi: I blame foreign media for my undoing
</title>
<body>
The former Italian prime minister claimed his image was ‘ruined’, insisting he had done ‘nothing wrong’.
He said: ‘It’s something that the foreign press have all fallen for.
‘It’s as if we have achieved nothing in the three years that we have been in power. My image has been ruined by things that are absolutely untrue.’
The 75-year-old, who resigned this month after losing his parliamentary majority, is involved in a series of sex scandals around his infamous bunga bunga parties.
Today, Nicole Minetti, 25, Lele Mora, 55, and Berlusconi’s best friend Emilio Fede, 80, stand trial accused of procuring women for the parties which regularly took place at the former leader’s Rome villa.
On Wednesday, the media tycoon’s trial for allegedly having sex with an underage prostitute will resume, while he is also facing other trials for perjury and fraud.
For both sex cases, footballer Cristiano Ronaldo and Hollywood star George Clooney are expected to be called as defence witnesses.
Berlusconi is said to have been taped referring to himself as a ‘part-time prime minister’ because he was so sexually active.
Meanwhile, a survey in La Repubblica revealed half of Italians thought he would make a comeback.
</body>
<url>
http://www.metro.co.uk/news/882319-silvio-berlusconi-i-blame-foreign-media-for-my-undoing
</url>
</doc>
</documents>